https://ncreview.com.au/privacystatement/

your password
Forgot your password?
your email
A password will be e-mailed to you.
News
AllAnimalsArtAutoBusinessCommunityCouncilCOVID-19CrimeDevelopmentEducationEntertainmentEnvironmentFeaturedFinanceFood & DrinkHealthHome & GardenKidsLocal HistoryMusicProjectsRetailRoadsRuralSafetyTechnologyTransportYouth
Fire destroys school
Upgrades to schools
Business support
Historic cottage to be restored
Sport
AllAthleticsBasketballBowlsCheerleadingCricketFootballGolfMotorsportNetballRacingRugbySoccer
Whittlesea tops Thomastown
Golf sensation sensation claims first win
Rain robs Wallan
Seymour district cricket washed out
Classifieds/Trades & Services
Classifieds
Review Business Directory
Editions
Web Privacy Statement
The North Central Review Pty Ltd, its subsidiaries and its publications respects your personal information and your right to privacy. We are committed to working with our customers and readers and we know that when you give us your personal information, we are committed to protecting your personal information and maintaining your trust.
Our Privacy Policy ensures we comply with the Australian Privacy Principles in the way that we collect, use and disclose personal information, and it is important to us that you know how your data is collected and used by us.
The North Central Review Pty Ltd may use personal information provided by you to ensure that we continue to provide our advertisers and readers with the best possible range of products and services. We may collect information about you when you use our services or purchase our products, enter into an advertising contract; email us, register or subscribe to be part of any of our digital products, engage in social media i.e. Facebook or enter into one of our competitions. The North Central Review Pty Ltd may share information to external service and data providers, government departments; that help us provide and manage our specialised products and services.
You may forward comments or questions about our service anonymously, however this may affect how efficiently we are able to deal with any concerns you may have.
Personal information collected in the course of journalism will be handled appropriately complying with the Australian Press Council Privacy Standards.
If your personal information is incorrect or out of date, or you would like to request access to the information we hold about you, please contact us.
Our Privacy Policy is published on our website for customers and employees and outlines in more detail the information that may be collected by Newspaper House Pty Ltd.
Your use of The North Central Review Pty Ltd website constitutes an acknowledgement that you have been made aware of our Privacy Policy.
We have the right to update our Privacy Policy at any time and are not obligated to bring it to your attention, the onus is on the reader to keep themselves up to date.
We would also like to hear from you if you have any concerns about your privacy or you have any query on how your personal information is collected or managed.
You can write to us outlining your concerns addressed to:
The General Manager
Phone: (03) 5734 3344
Email: gm@newspaperhouse.com.au
Write: 3/87 Sydney Street, KILMORE, VIC 3764
You can also obtain further general information about your privacy rights and privacy law from the Office of the Australian Information Commissioner:
